51 Woodard Dr Bristol, CT 06010

OFFICE SUPPORT PROFESSIONAL

PROFILE

Management experience, with the ability to easily establish rapport and trust with both, customers and colleagues. Result oriented, working proactively to ensure a positive end result with strong time management skills, as well as strong organizational skills. Outstanding customer service aptitude, with 15 years experience and excellent interpersonal skills consistently meet and exceed targeted results. Having dealt with a broad diversity of people, can offer the ability to identify problems and implement solutions. Able to prioritize and manage conflicting demands. Computer skills include *Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint, Publisher* and *Internet savvy*.

CORE SKILLS

Time Management
 Budgeting
 Word Processing
 Detail Oriented
 Organization
 Customer Service
 Ordering
 Reception

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

BRISTOL HOSPITAL COUNSELING CENTER Bristol, CT 2007-2009

Secretary

Created and updated patient charts, as well as status and program transfers in the computer.

Assisted the therapist on updating treatment plans.

Assisted the financial counselor in obtaining benefits and eligibility on new patients.

Ordered office and facility supplies.

Worked closely with the business office with corrections to patient's accounts.

Bristol Housing Authority Bristol, CT 2007-2007 **Temporary Office Assistant**

 $\hfill \Box$ Prepare and submit payroll for maintenance department.

- □ Made follow-up calls when needed.
- □ Created files for new sales contracts and organize existing files.
- □ Create letters for distribution to tenants regarding information from the maintenance department.

Crystal Rock Watertown, CT 2003-2004

Customer Service Rep

- Create customer order tickets.
- □ Submit updated payment and address changes.
- Research any discrepancies on orders and correct as necessary.
- ☐ Made follow-up calls when needed on order changes or corrections on accounts.

Michele L. Torres

Rent-A-Center Waterbury, CT 2002-2003 **Accounts Manager** Contract review with new and existing customers. Contact customers regarding pickup or delivery of merchandise. Merchandising and daily maintenance of showroom. Performed end of day closeout, printing daily sales report and balancing out the register. Prepare bank deposit. Waterbury, CT **Kmart** 1995-2002 **Softlines Division Manager** Supervise 25-100 associates. Training of new associates. Budget and scheduling of Softlines Division. Conduct daily meeting with associates, attend daily meetings with management staff. Conduct annual review of associates and department managers. Daily review of sales with each department setting a higher sales goal for the day. Daily review of jewelry audit, working with loss prevention on any discrepancies. Implementing layout changes with department managers and associates Attend meetings and workshop to learn and improve ways to boost morale and division sales. Work daily with the cash office reviewing and signing off on bank deposits. Distribution and collection of register bags when opening and closing the store.

EDUCATION

Brio Academy of Cosmetology, Meriden, New Haven November 2005 - February 2007 Certificate of completion

Goodwin College One to One, East Hartford, Hartford October 2004 - December 2004 Certificate of completion, in Medical/Dental Office Procedures

> Drake Business School, Manhattan, New York September 1993 - April 1995